Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Women of Hope Poster Sets 6084 G
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Women of Hope Poster Sets
1994- 1999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees (NUHHCE)
Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union
6084 G
4.5 cubic feet
2.5 linear ft.
Records, graphics.
5793338
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 23, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Scope and Contents
Box 1 contains study guides and brochures for poster sets. The poster sets, folders 2-19, are stored in the map case. Each set consists of 12 18-inch-by-24-inch posters.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6085 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project "Frederick Douglass and His Time" Posters 6089 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Posters 6084 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Women of Hope Poster Sets 6069: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Additional Files 6140: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project 6140 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio Recordings 5929 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs 5929: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Records 6169 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 6169: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Files 6169 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 6169 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs 5929 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 5929 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia
Women -- United States; Indian women -- United States; Hawaiian women -- United States; Hispanic American women -- United States; African American women -- United States; Bread and Roses Cultural Project; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199
5793338
- Women of Hope: African Americans Who Made A Difference, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Study Guide
- Women of Hope: African Americans Who Made A Difference, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Brochure
- Women of Hope: Latinas Abriendo Camino, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Women of Hope: Latinas Abriendo Camino, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Women of Hope: Native American / Hawaiian, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Women of Hope: Native American / Hawaiian, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Asian American Women of Hope, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Asian American Women of Hope, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- International Women of Hope, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- International Women of Hope, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Women of Hope: African-Americans Who Made a Difference/Latinas Abriendo Camino., 1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Posters
- Women of Hope: Latinas Abriendo Camino., 1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Women of Hope: Native American/Hawaiian., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Asian American Women of Hope., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Women of Hope: Native American/Hawaiian., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Women of Hope: Native American/Hawaiian., 1997 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Women of Hope: Native American/Hawaiian., 1997 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Women of Hope: Native American/Hawaiian., 1997 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- International Women of Hope., 1999 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- International Women of Hope., 1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- International Women of Hope., 1999 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Women of Hope: African-Americans Who Made a Difference., 1994 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Women of Hope: African-Americans Who Made a Difference., 1994 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Women of Hope: African-Americans Who Made a Difference., 1994 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Women of Hope: African-Americans Who Made a Difference., 1994 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous., 1995 (Box 21, Folder 5)